(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-14T22:39:51.702864",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Thank you all for joining us today for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
みなさま、本日はハコス・ベールズ生誕祭2026にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you all so much for coming today to Hakos Baelz's Birthday Celebration 2026.
開演に先立ちまして、みなさまにお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the show, we have some requests and guidance for you.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないように気をつけてください。
You are welcome to eat and drink in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは「#ReCOLOR3D」です。
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
Please post a lot about us on social media!
開演中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上がってくださいますと幸いです。
We would love it if you could post them to help build up the excitement.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait a moment until the show begins.
Thank you all for joining us today for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はハコス・ベールズ生誕祭2026にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you all so much for coming today to Hakos Baelz's Birthday Celebration 2026.
開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the show, we have some requests and guidance for you.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないように気をつけてください。
You are welcome to eat and drink in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは「#ReCOLOR3D」です。
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
Please post a lot about us on social media!
開演中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上がってくださいますと幸いです。
We would love it if you could post them to help build up the excitement.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait a moment until the show begins.
光の速さで 駆け抜ける衝動は
The urge to run through at the speed of light...
何を犠牲にしても 叶えたい強さの覚悟
...is the determination to make it reality, whatever the sacrifice.
No fear! 一度きりの
No fear! At this once-in-a-lifetime...
Trust you! この瞬間に
...trust you! ...moment,
賭けてみろ自分を信じて
take a gamble and believe in yourself!
時には運だって 必要と言うのなら
If you say that sometimes you even need luck...
宿命の旋律も 引き寄せてみせよう
...then I will draw even the melody of fate to myself!
走れ 今を まだ終われない
Run! The present cannot end yet!
辿り着きたい場所があるから
Because there is a place I want to reach!
その先へと進め
Move forward, beyond that place!
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Embracing even my tears tightly to my chest!
そこから始まるストーリー
The story starts from there,
果てしなく続く winning the soul
endlessly continuing... winning the soul!
掴め今を変えたいなら
Seize it! If you want to change the present,
描いた夢を未来に掲げ
hoist your envisioned dream to the future,
恐れないで挑め
don't be afraid, and challenge!
走れ 今を まだ終われない
Run! The present cannot end yet,
辿り着きたい場所があるから
because there is a place I want to reach!
その先へと進め
Move forward, beyond that place!
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Embracing even my tears tightly to my chest!
そこから始まるストーリー
The story starts from there,
果てしなく続く winning the soul
endlessly continuing... winning the soul!
Wow wow wow
What's up, everyone!
I am Chaos, the End of Events,
a sewer rat trapped in the cage of your device,
your best friend, Baelz Hakos from Hololive English -Promise-!
我こそはカオス、終わりの果て、ザ・エンド、
I am Chaos, the ultimate end, The End,
降臨の肉粉砕機、黄金の薔薇、
the advent of the meat grinder, the golden rose,
万事の主、ホロライブEnglishのハコス・ベールズです！
the master of all, Hakos Baelz of Hololive English!
Witness me!
Another year,
another not-birthday live!
Thank you so much for coming, everyone!
Did you like the opening act?
The opening show, did ya? Did ya?
Thank you so much for coming, everyone!
This year,
we have a not-birthday birthday live again called
ReCOLOR3D!
That is also the hashtag, please use it!
ReCOLOR3D. Um, I know it might be...
The theme this year was color, for... for many reasons.
There's also a lot of special things that are happening today,
as you may or may not already know,
there's a lot of new things being revealed in this live.
Maybe a new song?
Maybe a new outfit?
I don't know! You're just gonna have to wait and see.
えっと、今年も
Well, this year as well,
誕生日じゃない誕生日ライブやりたいと思います！
I'm holding a not-birthday birthday live!
みんな来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much to everyone for coming!
えー、今日のライブでね、
And, in today's live,
新しいものいっぱいあると思いますので
there are going to be a lot of new things,
最後まで見、見、見てくれたら嬉しいです！
so I'd be really happy if you watched until the end!
あ、もう疲れてる。やばい。はい！
Ah, I'm already tired. Oh no. Okay!
あの、ハッシュタグもぜひぜひ、
Also, please use the hashtag,
いっぱいコメントと写真をポストしてください！ありがとうございます！
and post lots of comments and photos! Thank you!
えっと、um, it is my birthday...
Um, it is my birthday...
...not birthday, but...
I'm just so excited to be able to share this day with all of you!
Once I catch my breath,
we're gonna get this party started, yeah?
じゃあ、最後まで楽しんでください！
Well then, please enjoy until the end!
そこ、次の曲ね、ちょっと...
For the next song...
I'm gonna go to the other stage for the next song,
so I'll see you guys there, all right? I'm gonna go now.
Um, is that all right? Okay, bye, see you guys there!
Race you!
ハァ
Ha!
あれが正解なんて
If that is the correct answer...
誰の成れの果て
...whose ruined end is it?
なんだっての悶々...
(What is it? Agonizing...)
答えも欲しいのも一個てこれだけ
The answer and what I want, is only this one thing.
悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
There's no use worrying about it, right?
あれは夢だったって思うことにしたって
Even if I decide to think that it was just a dream...
でも全然思えないんだけど
...I can't think of it that way at all.
助けてよフォロワー
Help me, followers!
抗うだけ
Just resisting,
若さに負け
succumbing to youth.
next , next , lucky , lucky , lucky
Next, next, lucky, lucky, lucky.
割り切れたらさ
If I could just accept it,
楽なのにとか
it would be so much easier...
もうヤダ～
...I'm so sick of this.
なんて新世界か！
What a brand new world!
あなた以外は...
Except for you...
あなた以外はいらない
...I don't need anyone else.
はらないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier.
あるはずなの何か
There must be something.
あったならば happy ! , jumpin ' , yeah !
If there is, then happy!, jumpin', yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしのこの手を
If we connect your hand with my hand,
つないだらもう二度と離さないわ
I will never let go of it again.
あなたのその手があたしのこの手を
If your hand grabs my hand...
掴んだら... 以後お見知りおきを！ my love
...from then on, please get to know me! My love.
これで終わりなんて
To say this is the end,
アガれないままなんて
without even getting hyped...
鳴いちゃってポンポンポン
(Ringing out, bang bang bang)
どうにかなっちゃえって願って願って
I keep wishing and wishing that something would happen,
ねぇ朝帰りしたりしちゃわん？どう？
Hey, how about staying out all night? What do you say?
なあもう我慢できん！
Man, I can't take this anymore!
pain , pain 痛いってば everydaySafe
Pain, pain, it hurts everyday,
ま、ゆーていけるけどなブルベ夏なんて関係ないな
but I can still get by. Cool summer tone doesn't matter.
誰よりもネコ 節操ないも結構
More of a cat than anyone, no principles is fine too.
あーしはあーしだ見といてよ ready
I am who I am, so keep your eyes on me, ready?
もう今日で終わらせたいなって
Thinking that I want to end this today...
リスタートできたらって
...and if I could restart...
でも無理よもう
...but it's impossible now.
what 's on your mind ?
What's on your mind?
割り切れたらさ
If I could just accept it,
楽なのにとか
it would be so much easier...
もうヤダ～
...I'm so sick of this.
なんて新世界か！
What a brand new world!
あなた以外は...
Except for you...
あなた以外はいらない
...I don't need anyone else.
はらないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier.
あるはずなの何か
There must be something.
あったならば happy ! , jumpin ' , yeah !
If there is, then happy!, jumpin', yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしのこの手を
If we connect your hand with my hand,
つないだらもう二度と離さないわ
I will never let go of it again.
あなたのその手があたしのこの手を
If your hand grabs my hand...
掴んだら... 以後お見知りおきを！ my love
...from then on, please get to know me! My love.
Oh, oh...
お見知りおきを！ my love
Please get to know me! My love.
ラリラリラッタ ラリラ
Lari lari latta, lari la.
Hey!
breakaway breakaway 最高level あの記号にgetされてる
Breakaway, breakaway, highest level, getting captured by that symbol.
姿 仕草 ok でしょ don't you think? don't you think?
My appearance and gestures are perfect, right? Don't you think? Don't you think?
アンソロジー 多分 top of top 並べてるだけのヒト
An anthology, probably top of the top, just people lined up.
crash crash 多数決 don't you think? don't you think?
Crash, crash, by majority vote. Don't you think? Don't you think?
in this world この頭には
In this world, inside this head...
what a beautiful mind 散る花びら
...what a beautiful mind, falling flower petals.
ハラハラ ひらひらり
Fluttering and falling down.
Hey!
誰もが歌いたい
Everyone wants to sing,
C R A Z Y
C-R-A-Z-Y!
一瞬の感情に
With a fleeting emotion...
ride on ride on ride on ride on
心もないさい
There is no heart either,
狂気のサムライ
the samurai of madness.
血走る目線で
With bloodshot eyes,
ready to die
体温は上り あなたの空 まっ暗な空
The body temperature rises, your sky is a pitch black sky.
荒々しく響き 千切れて
Resounding roughly, torn to shreds.
ほらその場所で 聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
Look, in that place, the trick of the beating heart can be heard.
轟くのは己の調べ
What thunders is my own melody.
誰かのじゃない 己の調べ
Not someone else's, but my own melody.
rat-tat rat-tat
目の前に広がる世界はブルー
The world spreading before my eyes is blue,
とりあえずさあ move move
for now, come on, move, move!
tick-tack tick-tack
there is no need 何その張り切って偉そうに
There is no need, why are you acting so enthusiastic and self-important?
君も愛を
You too, love...
右も左も
...both right and left...
知りもしないで言わないで
...don't say anything without even knowing.
don't you think? don't you think?
ニヤリ 影が笑う
Grinning, the shadow laughs.
世界はだいたい
The world is mostly...
C R A Z Y
...C-R-A-Z-Y!
繰り返すように
As if repeating...
ride on ride on ride on ride on
分かってもいない
You don't even understand,
あれこれと liar
this and that, liar!
Tell me something for the new
意外な 期待な 時代のバイブ
...unexpected, anticipated, vibe of the era.
Clap back
Lose my mind, shooting my sign
Save it あなたのその瞬間 Maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong
Save it, that moment of yours, maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong.
Ladi-ladi-atta ladi-ladi-da
Hey! これも砕いた
Hey! This too was crushed.
Hey! C-R-A-Z-Y
Hey! 一瞬の感情に Right on, right on, right on, right on
Hey! On this split-second emotion, right on, right on, right on, right on!
Hey! 心は Ninety-five
Hey! My heart is at ninety-five.
Hey! よれる侍
Hey! A staggering samurai.
Hey! 血走らせた目で行く
Hey! Going with bloodshot eyes.
Ready, ready to die
Hello 今は上り あなたの空 まっ黒な空
Hello, I'm rising now, into your sky, the pitch-black sky.
あら あら 地球引きちぎって
My, my, tear the Earth apart.
ほら その場所で聞こえてくる言葉仕掛け
Look, in that place, the trickery of words can be heard.
驚くのは誰 これから これ、これ、これ、これから
Who will be surprised? From now on, from, from, from, from now on!
あの街は狂い咲いて
That town is in mad full bloom...
時計の針 レジの街
...hands of the clock, cash register town.
猛々しく行く いざ Raise your voice
Going fiercely, now raise your voice!
Uh-huh, uh-huh
ほら すぐそこで始まり出すここの宴
Look, right there, this banquet is beginning.
離れるのは誰 のれの調べ
Who is leaving? The melody of my curtain.
唯一無二の のれの調べ
The one and only melody of my curtain.
B-B-Bijin しろ注意
Be, be, beware of that beauty.
あいつの信者は多い
She's got a lot of fanatics.
己を知りなさい bitch
Know yourself, bitch.
HDで見えるのに
Even though you can see it in HD.
私もあなた様みたいになりたい
Oh, I wanna look like you.
教えて 教えて 幸せですよね？
Tell me, tell me, you must be happy, right?
もしこのまま消えたら愛されるのなら
If i disappear this way and end up being loved...
今すぐにでも綺麗に亡くなりたい
...I would gladly die right now, beautifully.
こんなはずないわよダヴィンチ
This isn't how it should be, Da Vinci.
もう少しだけべっぴんに
Make me just a little bit prettier.
コントラストも入れて頂戴
Add some contrast in there, too.
全世界を懲らしめたい
I wanna punish the whole world.
Look at this
Look at this, uh.
Look at this 悲しいかも ey ey ey
Look at this, it's a bit sad, ey ey ey.
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Give my skin a bit more glow.
女盛り舐めたらヤイ
Don't mess with a woman in her prime, hey.
トイレに女神はおったんかい？
Did you find the goddess in the bathroom?
おったなら捕まえなさい
If you did, better catch her.
ちゃんみな最近マジかわいい
Chanmina is so pretty nowadays.
私は忘れないあの嵐
I'll never forget that storm.
あの時私はまだ seventeen
Back then I was only seventeen.
あの時言ったよな
Remember what you said to me back then?
You can't be beautiful, you can't be famous
みにくいブスが歌ってんじゃないよ
An ugly bitch like you shouldn't be a singer.
あの時狂った精神に才能が開花
As my mind grew insane back then, my talent blossomed.
あじわった幸福も不幸も一般じゃなかった
Every happiness and unhappiness I went through was unordinary.
本物を君は知るてるかい？
Have you ever seen the real thing?
知識と経験のエロス
Eros of knowledge and experience.
まだ使いもんになってるかい？
Do you still have it in you?
女はみんな正気じゃない
Women, we're all insane.
I am beautiful!
Look at this
Look at this, uh.
Look at this 悲しいかも ey ey ey
Look at this, it's a bit sad, ey ey ey.
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Give my skin a bit more glow.
女盛り舐めたらヤイ
Don't mess with a woman in her prime, hey.
トイレに女神はおったんかい？
Did you find the goddess in the bathroom?
おったなら捕まえなさい
If you did, better catch her.
Can you hear me mina are you the beauty
Say July you are the true fucking beauty
Say truly, you are the true fucking beauty.
予想違い驚きなさい
Be surprised, I'm not what you predicted.
磨いたらダイヤ 美しい
Polish me and I'm a diamond, beautiful.
悲観的 いや美学的
Pessimistic? No, aesthetical.
磨いたらダイヤ 美しい
Polish me and I'm a diamond, beautiful.
生きなさい 今見せなさい
Live and enchant right now.
あなたこそダイヤ 美しい
You are the diamond, beautiful.
I'm a fucking woman and I'm fucking beautiful
God, here I am
We're fucking women and we're fucking beautiful
Yeah!
Ah! Ah!
Look, everyone! I finally have a new outfit!
見て、見て、見て！新衣装どう？可愛い？どう？
Look, look, look! How is my new outfit? Is it cute? How is it?
どう？どう？どう？
How is it? How is it? How is it?
But look, it's...
It's performance Bae!
Ah!
You want to have a close up?
There's things, there's so many things I want to show off!
Starting from... let's start from the top, top-down, from the head.
Look at that...
Look at that hair! Look at that fade!
かっこよくない？
Isn't it cool?
I asked for a wolf cut,
um, that's also half up, half down,
so it's really easy to dance in.
めちゃくちゃ踊りやすくて
It's super easy to dance in...
可愛いでしょ？ま、可愛い、カッコいいでしょ？アハ、アハハハ
...and cute, right? Well, cute and cool, right? Aha, ahahaha!
And then, uh, what else, what else? Oh, my makeup!
メイクも可愛いでしょ？
My makeup is cute too, right?
And then I have so many, like, hand accessories as well!
Look at that! Look at that!
Look how cool that is!
And then we do like a quick scan of the...
T-pose quick scan! Quick scan of the body!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
There's also something very special.
I have an MC tail now. If you noticed...
...earlier, normally when I dance, I have my...
...tail just, you know, free, but...
...you know, this is the MC resting tail...
...cause the tail also needs resting periods as well, so...
...this is my MC tail.
Very cute! I hope you guys like it!
Oh my god! And this was designed by...
...of course, the amazing Mika-mama!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much!
めちゃくちゃ可愛いデザインになりました
It turned out to be an incredibly cute design!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much!
But that's not all!
I mean, if I get a new outfit, I feel like...
...it's only fair that...
...some other people get new outfits!
来て！来て！来て！
Come here! Come here! Come here!
The Bae Dancers also get new outfits!
You get an outfit, you get an outfit, everyone gets an outfit! Look at them!
Oh! Oh, look! Oh yeah, oh wow!
Oh, so sexy! Oh!
So the Bae Dancers have also upgraded outfits!
They have shorts with the boots, and the socks, and the jacket!
Wow! Look at that! Amazing!
And then on the back of the jacket they have my logo!
後ろにロゴもあります
There's also a logo on the back!
可愛い！
Cute!
I also designed... well, not designed, but...
...I wanted the design to be easy for them to dance in as well, so...
This is the upgraded Bae Dance Team!
どう？可愛い？
How is it? Cute?
ポーズ
Pose.
ポーズ！
Pose!
可愛い！
Cute!
まあ、せっかくなんでね
Well, since we have this opportunity...
Since we all have new outfits, I think it's only fitting that we continue the rest of the live...
...like this, with our new outfits!
じゃあ、踊りましょうか！
Now then, shall we dance!
We're gonna do the next song on the stage over there.
行くよ！
Here we go!
ほい！ほい！よいしょ！よいしょ！よいしょ！
Hoi! Hoi! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Wow!
よいしょ！よいしょ！緊張するな
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! I'm nervous.
はい！
Yes!
じゃ、どうぞ！
Well then, please enjoy!
正体あらわせ
Reveal your true identity!
月の光を飲む
Drinking the moonlight,
僕の夜が来た
my night has arrived.
けたたましく現れる one, two
Appearing with a clamor, one, two,
危険を探して knock, knock, knock!
searching for danger, knock, knock, knock!
Don't mess it up! Forget it, make a finger!
窓を見て you can see my eyes
Look at the window, you can see my eyes.
その瞳に出会ったら
Once our eyes meet,
お前は仲間だ カム カム say it!
you're one of us, come, come, say it!
けしやうのものか
Is it a phantom?
ましやうのものか
Is it a demon?
正体あらわせ ay, ta-da-da-da-da
Reveal your true identity, ay, ta-da-da-da-da!
変装して love it 僕 見て know it
Disguised, love it, look at me, know it.
らいらい らいらいや
Rai-rai, rai-rai-ya!
明かせ love it 存在 know it
Reveal, love it, existence, know it.
いないいないばぁ
Peek-a-boo!
Don't worry, 傷つけないよ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
ライアイア
Lai-ai-a!
I let you このミステリーに
I'll let you into this mystery,
アイヤイヤイヤイヤイヤ
ai-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya!
See this finger trap!
明日は make it rough
Tomorrow, make it rough.
今日は make it fire
Today, make it fire.
目を避けないで make loud your voice
Don't look away, make your voice loud.
よし よし 止め 恐れ
There, there, stop the fear,
お狐様に任せよ！
leave it all to the fox!
光を騙して作るんだ night
Tricking the light to create the night,
あちこち目覚めて 闇が喝采
awakening here and there, the darkness applauds.
ねぇ ほら こっちおいで
Hey, look, come over here.
Yeah, just shout out the spell!
けしやうのものか
Is it a phantom?
ましやうのものか
Is it a demon?
正体あらわせ ay, ta-da-da-da-da
Reveal your true identity, ay, ta-da-da-da-da!
未体験 love it 僕は know it
Inexperience, love it, I know it.
らいらい らいらいや
Rai-rai, rai-rai-ya!
この世界変える see me
Change this world, see me.
期待して
Look forward to it.
Don't worry, 傷つけないよ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
ライアイア
Lai-ai-a!
I let you さあ 魅魅魅魅に
I'll let you into the charms,
アイヤイヤイヤイヤイヤ
ai-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya!
Hey! Follow the queen fox!
I'm the real master of this night!
Hey! Follow your queen fox!
魅せられて 魅せられて dan, dan, dan
Charmed, charmed, step by step...
重なり合った
...overlapping...
僕たちの show window
...our show window.
見透かすこの眼差し 君に届いてる？
Is this piercing gaze reaching you?
Why don't you know?
It's time now!
どんな姿でも構わない世界へ
To a world where any appearance is fine!
けしやうのものか
Is it a phantom?
ましやうのものか
Is it a demon?
正体あらわせ
Reveal your true identity!
Shut up, let love win!
Hands up! And set the love 僕みたいのは lie lie lie lie lie
Hands up! And set the love, someone like me is just lie lie lie lie lie
Hands up! And set the love 存在のない nay nay nay nay nay
Hands up! And set the love, non-existent, nay nay nay nay nay
Don't worry 傷つけないよ lie lie lie
Don't worry, I won't hurt you, lie lie lie
I'll let you call me Mr. Video, ay-ay-ay-ay-ay!
I'll let you search for me, more journey, ay-ay-ay-ay-ay! This finger trap!
Just shout out the spell!
Woah... oh... oh... oh... oh...
Yeah! Follow Queen Fox!
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
時には噛んだりして 痛みを覚えさせて
Sometimes biting down, make me remember the pain
溢れる液体で汚してよ 全部
Stain everything with the overflowing fluid
足の先からずっと 這わせたその神経はもう
Those nerves that crawled all over, from my toes up
感触に溺れる 身体ココロを連れて<
Are drowning in sensation, taking my body and heart with them
指くわえた我慢の中
In the midst of biting my finger in patience...
欲してんのが理想？
...is what you're desiring the ideal?
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need any of it
磨き上げてる邪魔なPRIDE
My polished, obstructive pride
無意味な世界のルールくらい 無駄としか言い様がない
Something like the rules of this meaningless world, I can only describe it as useless
隠しているあなたのSTYLE 剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
The style you are hiding, dive with it laid bare
そこに生まれるのは期待 外れなんかじゃない
What is born there is expectation, it's not a mistake
頂のSMILE
The smile at the peak
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
吐息を合わせた相性 耳に吹きかける感情
Compatibility with matched breathing, emotion blown into my ear
破裂しそうな胸騒ぎだす細胞
My chest feels like it's going to burst, my cells starting to stir
脱ぎかけてるシャツ 優しく裂いてよ まず
First kindly rip off this shirt I'm taking off, no worries
かまわず get
Without caring, get...
フライングも有り 躊躇わないで darlin'
Flying starts are allowed, don't you dare hesitate, darlin'
自由な世界のど真ん中
Right in the middle of a free world...
夢見てんのが本性？
Is dreaming your true nature?
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need any of it
怯気づいた野望のTRY
That try of a timid ambition
満足なんてそこにない 目に見える哀れな未来
Satisfaction is surely not there in that clearly miserable future
思い通りにできるLIFE 手にできるかはあなた次第
Live life as you please, making it your own depends on you
隠したりなんかはしない
Don't waste time hiding it...
誰よりも誇らしげにできるMIND
Do what's on your mind more proudly than anyone
ほらこの世界の中他にはない
Look, in this world there is nothing else
確かなもの 自分以外は皆無
The only certain thing is yourself
小さくなってる場合じゃない
There's no time to shrink back!
She's on top of the world, why stop now? We got no time, all right!
Don't get cheap, go engine, 全開で
Don't get cheap, go engine, full throttle...
いっちゃえ BURN, BURN, BURN!
Go on and burn, burn, burn!
欲しがってんのはそう 気持ちいいの more...
What you want, yes, is to get more of that great feeling...
あるがままの想いでDANCE! イイナリでGET DOWN!
So dance the way you feel like right now, do as you're told and get down!
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need any of it
磨き上げてる邪魔なPRIDE
A shined-up, obtrusive pride
無意味な世界のルールくらい 無駄としか言い様がない
As for the rules of this meaningless world, it's pointless to describe them
隠しているあなたのSTYLE 剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
Your style is hidden away, but dive with it laid bare
そこに生まれるのは期待 外れなんかじゃない
What's born there is hope, it's not a mistake
頂のSMILE
The smile at the peak
ほらこの世界で今解き放て
Right now in this world, let them out
鋭くギラつかせた希望
Your sharp, dazzling hopes
もっと本気出していいよ<
You gotta let out your determination even more
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ow! Huh... come chase me.
Everyday I spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
On the way, yeah, my heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead and...
Now they say I, I'm just a masochist, they're sick of it
Boy, take a hint, you ain't gon' ever get this
Pedal to the metal, shootin' straight to the stars
Got a cravin', like the danger on me
Yeah, she like it like that, like that
Up another level, temptation you just can't deny
Come get a taste but can't say I won't bite
...gonna... ah!
In my eyes, nirvana...
Oh, I'm taking off now!
Pushing for the high,
my lover, I gotta run!
But it's fun to see you try.
So hit me up!
Off the map, I'mma take it, all my energy.
Speeding up fast, ready, target locked.
So hit me up!
Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece.
So hit me up, ah! I never stop!
In a new territory,
I'm on the edge of glory.
Boy, just watch how I move,
gimme that rush!
Got no regrets in my mind,
boy, it's on you this time.
So hit me up, outta luck, volume up,
you got a crush?
Such a cliché, your bad boy charms,
wasn't enough, you needed more.
Now you're begging to let you score,
surely you'll take it all in stride.
I'mma be busy tonight.
Goodbye, goodbye,
gotta leave you dry.
Always trying to play it cool,
20/20 vision on me.
Just outside my field of view...
Yeah, she like it like that, like that.
Engine booming, that's my cue,
catch me if you can, you better...
...keep up the chase,
boy, you're falling behind!
Supersonic, I'm heading out,
I'm gonna... ah!
In my eyes, nirvana...
Oh, I'm taking off now!
Pushing for the high,
my lover, I gotta run!
But it's fun to see you try.
So hit me up!
Off the map, I'mma take it, all my energy.
Speeding up fast, ready, target locked.
So hit me up!
Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece.
So hit me up, ah! I never stop!
In a new territory,
I'm on the edge of glory.
Boy, just watch how I move,
gimme that rush!
Got no regrets in my mind,
boy, it's on you this time.
So hit me up, outta luck, volume up,
you got a crush?
Ahh, just barely wasn't enough, you shoulda...
...ahh, given me all that you got, you coulda.
Coming full circle,
I hit a nerve, oh!
Top spot, getting hot,
watch me run it up!
So hit me up!
Rev it up and make that vroom vroom vroom vroom!
Hit me up!
When I hit you with that zoom zoom zoom zoom!
If you know what's good for you, ooh ooh ooh.
Feel me?
Now I'm back in charge,
rise out of the dark!
Yeah! I hope you enjoyed that!
Did you guys enjoy? Did you guys enjoy?
We had a couple of songs with, uh, a couple of important people, which I wanna call in...
...to help with this next MC part.
Special guests! Special guests!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What's up, everyone!
Yeah!
Introduce yourselves, please!
Please, go ahead.
ホロライブEnglish、CHADCASTの森カリオペです！
From Hololive English Chadcast, I'm Mori Calliope!
What's up? です、です、です。 Hey, guys!
What's up? Death, death, death. Hey, guys!
Hope you enjoyed our performances!
Yeah!
And IRyS! IRyS also from CHADCAST!
Yeah, let's go!
And Rumble!
Yeah!
What's this movement?
Did you say your name? Rumble?
I said Rumble. Oh, Rumble!
I'm pretty sure she said 'introduce yourselves'!
I'm pretty sure she said 'IRyS'!
My brain's not working!
It's because of the dancing.
It's a big day, guys.
Guys!
Yeah.
Oh, yeah! I mean, yeah, obviously. Woo!
What are you doing? It's so cool! So cool!
It looks dynamic.
You look like a K-pop star!
Oh, yeah!
I'm so glad you like it!
And look, the MC tail is back! You know, I've got to put it to rest for a little bit...
...after all that dancing. So special.
Yeah! Don't touch it, don't touch it.
But we performed some songs together.
First we had 'If...' oh god.
Oh, well, I guess it's on... on brand!
Yeah, we know.
Awesome. It's awesome, it's great!
That was a sexy song. How... how do you feel about that song?
Thank you so much.
How do I feel? Yeah. How do you feel about that song?
Feelings? Thoughts? Opinions?
I feel great about it!
I think it was amazing. She embraced her soul.
And... we also did... Hit... Hit...
So 'HIT ME UP'! 'HIT ME UP'!
It's so cool, yeah!
I'm so happy!
We practiced. We practiced so hard. Yeah, we did! We worked so hard.
It's so fun practicing together, though. Yeah!
Three of us, two of us at a time. It's always fun. Yeah, glad you liked it!
ねえ！
Yeah!
I'm so happy I'm able to dance with you guys on my birthday!
Not birthday! Birthday but not birthday.
On "un-birthday". On "un-birthday".
She's being "un-birthed".
But... That sounds so wrong!
Save it for the chat list! I'll save it for the chat list.
But after dancing, I am feeling a little bit, you know, hot!
Hot? It's getting hot in here? Is she gonna take off all her clothes?
Whoa! Age-restricted! Maybe not.
I'll be right back.
What is she taking off? Is she gonna take off her pants?
Why would she take off her pants, IRyS? What is she thinking about? Oh my God.
Why is she taking...? All right, you know what?
Stop, you need to be stopped. Oh, could it be? Oh, she's coming in.
Whoa! Behold!
I took off my jacket! Oh my God, she looks so fancy! So cool!
See, you can see all my, all my, all my accessories now.
かっこいい！ I love the spikes. Yeah!
Cool! I love the spikes. Yeah!
いいなそのポーズ。 But I have like an arm cuff now as well.
I like that pose. But I have like an arm cuff now as well.
Cool! Now I can dance even more with no restriction!
She's even more dynamic! More dynamic! My God.
More dynamic! Yeah, the pigtails don't get in the way either, like... Oh my God, she's popping off.
All the arms!
ま、せっかくなのでね。 Since we're all here together...
Well, since we're here anyway. Since we're all here together...
How would you guys feel about maybe doing one more song together?
Okay! I don't have the energy, but I'll do my best!
がんばれがんばれがんばれ！ イェーイ！
Do your best, do your best, do your best! Yay!
That being said, I hope you guys are ready as well. We're gonna bring you one more, chatcast... performance!
Ready, せーの… Let's go!
Ready, 1, 2... Let's go!
あじまう あじまう あじまーう！ 宿題が全ッ然終わらない、全国のヤバめな諸君！
It's starting, starting, starting! To all the guys nationwide whose homework isn't done at all!
時間がなければ眠らなきゃ良いじゃない
If you don't have time, why not just stay awake?
がんばれ がんばれ あたし！
Go for it, go for it, me!
パーリラ 脳内フロア 暴れてるカルナバル
Party-la! Inside my brain floor, a carnival is running wild!
アドレナリンドバドバ
Adrenaline is gushing out!
究極の PANIGHT
The ultimate PANIGHT!
パリナイ！パリナイ！ パーラパッパパリナイ！ パリナイ！パリナイ！ おわるくナイ？
Party night! Party night! Pa-la-pa-pa party night! Party night! Party night! It's not ending, is it?
We are NEGI☆U We are NEGI☆U We are NEGI☆U Let's go!
すごい ヤバい パない 物足りない ないない尽くしで とめどない
Amazing, crazy, insane, not enough! Endlessly lacking everything!
すごい ヤバい パない Saturday night とにかくもうやるしかない
Amazing, crazy, insane Saturday night! Anyway, we've just got to do this!
ヤバい パない 物足りない 全力モノモノ申したい
Crazy, insane, not enough! I want to speak my mind with all my might!
たった一度の青春は 毎日 enjoy party night
This once-in-a-lifetime youth... Enjoy a party night every day!
あーお集まりの旦那様 えーそうじゃない様 ご唱和ください決
Ah, gathered gentlemen, and those who aren't, sing along with us!
それゆけ say wow-wow wow-wow wow-wow
Let's go, say: Wow, wow! Wow, wow! Wow, wow!
D-D-D-DJ!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Everybody, sing along. でっち上げ進化論 陽キャでも陰キャでも 勉強だ wassup, wassup!
Everybody, sing along! Made-up theory of evolution! Extrovert or introvert, it's study time, wassup, wassup!
太陽は銀河系？ おしゃべりノンノンノン！
The sun is in the Milky Way? Stop talking, no, no, no!
遊んじゃダメダメごめんなさーい！
No playing around, sorry!
朝が来て眠れない どうしよう
Morning has come and I can't sleep! What should I do?
神様も両手挙げて fly high
Even God is raising hands to fly high!
なんとかするしかない がんばれ出来るって
We have no choice but to manage! Do your best, you can do it!
ド派手にかましちゃうね
We're gonna pull it off in a flash way!
ネバギバ put your hands up
Never give up, put your hands up!
タリナイ！タリナイ！ ターラタッタ タリナイ！ タリナイ！タリナイ！ 時間がない
Not enough! Not enough! Ta-la-ta-ta not enough! Not enough! Not enough! There's no time!
We are NEGI☆U We are NEGI☆U We are NEGI☆U Let's go!
（あ、えっと、れっつごー）
Woo, let's go.
すごい ヤバい パない 物足りない 代打のバッターかたじけない
Amazing, crazy, insane, not enough! Much obliged to the pinch hitter!
すごい ヤバい パない Sunday night とにかくもうやるしかない
Amazing, crazy, insane Sunday night! Anyway, we've just got to do this!
ヤバい パない 物足りない 宿題やっぱり終わらない
Crazy, insane, not enough! As expected, the homework is never ending!
たった一度の青春は 脳内 happy party night
This once-in-a-lifetime youth... A happy party night in my brain!
ねねちー、あてぃしー、おわんねーよこれー！
Nenechi, Atishi, this is never going to end!
スバル先輩！この問題全然わかんないんですけど！
Subaru-senpai! I don't understand this question at all!
えーっ！何その鉛筆！めっちゃ可愛いじゃん、いいなー！
Eh! What's with that pencil? It's super cute, I'm jealous!
でしょー！キラキラ光るんですよー、ホホホ
Right? It sparkles and shines! Ho-ho-ho!
あ、へへ、みんな、げんきだなぁ
Ah, hehe, everyone's so energetic.
よう、陽キャって、こんな時もすごいなー
Wow, extroverts are amazing even at times like this.
はははは… えと、はは、ぱ、ぱーりー！
Hahaha... Uh, haha, pa-party!
すごいヤバいパない物足りない...
Amazing, crazy, insane, not enough...
お書きになったそんな音楽、現代使われておりません。
The music you wrote is not used in this day and age.
もう一度お書き直しください。
Please rewrite it once more.
意味は完売
Meaning is sold out.
どうせ誰も聞いてなんかいないさ
Anyway, nobody is listening anyway.
音楽なんて全部ファッション
Music is all just fashion.
音楽なんてセンス対象外
Music is out of the question for taste.
どうせ何も伝えてなんかいないさ
Anyway, they're not conveying anything at all.
何万回もトクトクと最低な
Tens of thousands of times, to the worst thumping beat...
音楽に踊らされていくだけ
...we just go on being made to dance by music.
どうしたって どうみたって 創作者たちでも大渋滞
No matter what, no matter how you look at it, creators are in a huge traffic jam.
それもあっちこっちそっちぼっち 満足せんと演出をも欲しがる
And they still want directing without being satisfied here, there, and everywhere.
間違い欲しいの？
Do you want mistakes?
意味とかどちらだっていいよ
Either meaning or whatever is fine.
歌詞とかどうでもいいので
Since lyrics don't really matter...
乗れるのください
...please give us something we can groove to.
さあみんなで笑いましょう
Now, let's all laugh together.
芸術より数の代償
The price of numbers rather than art.
バイラルに酷い大衆
The terrible masses gone viral.
じゃあどうすんの？それでいいんだっけ？
So what are you going to do? Is that really fine?
頭は空回り死んでいく
My mind spins uselessly as it dies.
For myself instead
ふざけるな
Don't mess with me!
バイバイ、バズメロディ保存
Bye-bye, viral melody.
疑えよ 大概 嘘ばかり
Doubt them, they're mostly nothing but lies.
負けんな
Don't lose!
幻想でも理想でもいい
Whether a fantasy or an ideal, it's fine.
君の歌いたかったものはどうしたんだい？
What happened to the thing you wanted to sing?
死屍累々でもオールライト 嘘じゃない
Even as a heap of corpses, it's alright, it's not a lie.
おざなりに理想で満たす前に
Before negligently filling it with ideals...
負けんな
...don't lose!
覚醒せよ、子供達よ
Awaken, children!
君の伝えたかったものはどうしたんだい？
What happened to the thing you wanted to convey?
意味は完売
Meaning is sold out.
お書きになったそんな音楽、現代使われておりません。
The music you wrote is not used in this day and age.
ポップソング、ヒットソング聞いて、もう一度お書き直しください。
Listen to pop songs and hit songs, and please rewrite it once more.
嗚呼もう這い上がったからばっか小癪だわ
Ah, geez, you're just being cheeky because you crawled your way up!
どいつもこいつもそいつもあいつも
This guy, that guy, everyone...
意味は完売
...meaning is sold out.
どうしたって どうみたって 創作者たちでも大渋滞
No matter what, no matter how you look at it, creators are in a huge traffic jam.
それもあっちこっちそっちぼっち 満足せんと演出をも欲しがる
And they still want directing without being satisfied here, there, and everywhere.
間違い欲しいの？意味とかどちらだっていいよ
Do you want mistakes? Either meaning or whatever is fine.
歌詞とかどうでもいいので乗れるのください
Since lyrics don't really matter, please give us something we can groove to.
さあみんなで笑いましょう
Now, let's all laugh together.
芸術より数なんでしょう
It's about numbers rather than art, right?
バイラルに酷い代償
A terrible price for going viral.
じゃあどうすんの？それでいいんだっけ？
So what are you going to do? Is that really fine?
頭は空回り死んでいく
My mind spins uselessly as it dies.
For myself instead
ふざけるな
Don't mess with me!
バイバイ、バズメロディ 疑えよ 大概 嘘ばかり
Bye-bye, viral melody. Doubt them, they're mostly nothing but lies.
負けんな
Don't lose!
幻想でも理想でもいい 君の歌いたかったものはどうしたんだい？
Whether a fantasy or an ideal, it's fine. What happened to the thing you wanted to sing?
このままじゃ到底終われない
We absolutely can't end like this.
欲しいのはきっとお金じゃない
What we want is surely not money.
負けんな
Don't lose!
覚醒せよ、子供達よ 君の伝えたかったものを見つけんだ
Awaken, children! Find the thing you wanted to convey!
ふざけるな
Don't mess with me!
ふざけるな バイバイ、バズメロディ
Don't mess with me! Bye-bye, viral melody.
疑えよ 大概 嘘ばかり
Doubt them, they're mostly nothing but lies.
負けんな
Don't lose!
幻想でも理想でもいい 君の歌いたかったものはどうしたんだい？
Whether a fantasy or an ideal, it's fine. What happened to the thing you wanted to sing?
死屍累々でもオールライト 嘘じゃない おざなりに理想で満たす前に
Even as a heap of corpses, it's alright, it's not a lie. Before negligibly filling it with ideals...
負けんな
...don't lose!
覚醒せよ、子供達よ 僕の伝えたかったものはどうしたんだい？
Awaken, children! What happened to the thing I wanted to convey?
意味は完売
Meaning is sold out.
意味は完売よ
Meaning is totally sold out!
意味は完売
Meaning is sold out.
I'm a V.
Virtual blah blah blah blah? I'm a V.
Virtual blah blah blah blah? I'm a V
だ la vida な diva
...da la vida, a diva.
Love that blah blah blah
たかだか生身の魂胆
Just a flesh-and-blood ulterior motive,
さわらば可愛いの混沌
if touched, a cute chaos.
高天原からほら「堕としてあげる」
Look, from the High Celestial Plain, "I'll let you fall."
Hi, そう メンヘラでも面がキュートならメンキラー
Hi, yeah, even if you're unstable, if your face is cute, you're a men-killer.
とか貼られたレッテル逝ってるメンタルは
Labels like that are stuck on a dying mentality...
最強スマイルで 転がしてけファンダム
With a supreme smile, keep the fandom rolling.
誤魔化してる傷心性根
Disguising a wounded soul.
晒されたら引退にゃんてな
If exposed, then it's retirement—just kidding!
I am a V. I'm a V. I'm a 泡々よ
I am a V. I'm a V. I'm just bubbles.
I am la vida な diva 淫らは嫌よ
I am la vida, a diva, I hate being lewd.
夢見てる少年A 夢見てる少女A
Dreaming Boy A, dreaming Girl A.
Vならvidaは甘々甘々甘々の
If it's a V, then life is sweet, sweet, sweet...
No
ちょん切る我利我利妄想
Snipping off selfish delusions,
笑わせんな我がセンター
don't make me laugh, I'm the center.
誰よりも客寄せのパンダ
A panda drawing crowds more than anyone else,
ワレハナンダ？
what am I?
まるで膿んだ自己愛性生者
Like a festering narcissistic survivor.
Am I V? Am I C?
洗いざらい甘い汁 搾い（吸い）に
Sucking out every last drop of sweet juice,
我愛你
I love you.
Now, love me. ほら見舞えモンスター
Now, love me. Feast your eyes, monster.
My name is メラメラ 召されたら最後 メラメラ
My name is Mera Mera. If you're taken, it's the end, Mera Mera.
I'm a feeder なめんなタコ 心の中を smooth like a butter
I'm a feeder, don't mess with me. Through your mind, smooth like butter.
Touch me したいならほらエンドレス Catch me だハイピース
If you want to touch me, it's endless. Catch me with a peace sign.
めちゃ狂う都合がわからない
I don't understand how things get so crazy.
破れ心叫ぶ一つのライフ
With a torn heart, a single life screams out.
生きる姿や魂を今 二つにして 愛をバラバラに
Splitting my living form and soul into two, breaking love to pieces.
生まれた時の喜びは保障に さようならでいいな
With the joy of birth as collateral, saying goodbye is just fine.
だめね
No way.
わっちゃわっちゃ わっちゃわっちゃめっかめっか
Wacha wacha, wacha wacha mekka mekka
羅漢の露骨ね あらら傲慢で許可ね
Rakan is explicit, oh my, permitted through arrogance.
徹底正体ね あら わっちゃわっちゃめっかめっか
Your true identity is exposed. Oh, wacha wacha mekka mekka.
羅漢の露骨ね あらら傲慢で許可ね
Rakan is explicit, oh my, permitted through arrogance.
一巻の終わりね あら あらあらかしこ
This is the end of the chapter, oh my, sincerely yours.
I am a B, I am a B, I am a 泡々よ
I am a B, I am a B, I am flustered!
I am a ビー玉 ディーバ乱らわよ
I am a marble, a diva, I'm unruly.
夢見てる少年が 夢見てる少女で
The dreaming boy is a dreaming girl.
Bなラブ Bな泡泡泡泡泡泡 No!
B-grade love, B-grade bubbles, No!
強要さ子供の頃言われたもんだ
I was forced, told since I was a kid.
あのヒーローショーの人形の背中には
Behind the back of that hero show doll...
チャックは付いてないからね、泣くな！
...there is no zipper! Don't cry!
バーチャルだヒューマンだ死ぬのが優雅
Virtual or human, dying is elegant.
存在はワンワンだ 吠えても惚れても死ぬのはバラバラだ
Our existence is barking. Whether we howl or fall in love, we die in pieces.
わっちゃわっちゃ わっちゃわっちゃ
Wacha wacha, wacha wacha
わっちゃわっちゃわっちゃ Are you ready for?
Wacha wacha wacha, Are you ready for?
うん、惚れたら死ぬぞ
Yeah, if you fall in love, you die.
わっちゃわっちゃ わっちゃわっちゃ
Wacha wacha, wacha wacha
わっちゃわっちゃ
Wacha wacha
うん、I'm a B
Yeah, I'm a B.
Guys! I'm so tired!
I hope you guys have been enjoying the show! We had so many bangers after bangers after bangers!
A lot of dancing, we had Parade...
...we had Cyberpunk Dead Boy, we had...
...Mera Mera! My arms are dead, everything's dead.
But, that's not the end of the show yet! We gotta keep going on and on and on and on and on!
And here, I bring you a very, very, very important and...
...exciting announcement!
I am about to perform a song that no one has heard before!
No one! Except for me.
Because... it's my new song!
I've been hyping this up for a while now because I'm really, really excited...
...and this will be the first time that I'm sharing it with all of you, so I hope you enjoy.
More information after I perform it, because you gotta see it first, you know?
Wish me luck, I'm nervous, but...
...we got this! これから、私の新曲です！
...we got this! Up next is my new song!
あの、めっちゃ緊張なんだけど、がんばって...
Oh, I'm so nervous, but I'll do my best...
...パフォーマンスしたいと思います！
...to give a great performance!
どうぞ！
Here we go!
준비~!
Ready~!
That's good game, what a shame. Players, they all complain,
“Why me?” “No, not again!” Shout! Ratatata, but!
Ain't got time so dry those eyes. Look around, what's that I spy?
The broken and bruised all got something to prove now.
Abracadabra, let's go.
Watch them like dice as they fall.
끝까지 가보자 go!
Let's go to the end, go!
나는 내 맘대로 해, hey!
I do whatever I want, hey!
Double one, double win, lowly to lottery.
Do or die, we hit that high.
Snake eyes, snake eyes.
Come on now, don't be shy.
뜨겁게 달아올라
Heat up intensely.
놀자 all day all night
Let's play all day all night.
So turn it up, can't stop, won't stop preaching.
Who said the sky's the limit?
Show them that we mean business.
We are the young and vicious.
Snake eyes, they never lie.
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind.
지겨워!
I'm sick of this!
우리들의 광란의 party
Our frenzied party.
보여줄게 환상 safari
I'll show you a fantasy safari.
Baddie baddie, nobody can stop me.
끼리끼리 붙어, come on closer!
Birds of a feather, come on closer!
Go, go, 더 빨리!
Go, go, faster!
Actin' all naughty.
싹 다 부셔 모조리
Shatter it all to pieces.
모조리 싹 다 다 다 다!
Every single last bit!
Shake it off, what goes around...
shake it off, what goes around
shut your mouth, will come back down
ready to fight, ready to scream
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch it, we reap in it all
(reap in it all)
꺾이지 않는 의지
An unyielding will
될 대로 돼 볼래, play
Let happen what will, let's play
Reason, our demon
Believe in the beaten
Just wait and see
We hit that high
Snake eyes, snake eyes
Come on now, don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라
It's heating up
(불타올라)
(Burn up)
놀자 all day, all night
Let's play all day, all night
(all day, all night)
놀자 all day, all night
Let's play all day, all night
(all night)
Let the beat drop!
Go!
We go hard! (go hard)
기사회생, 전부를 걸어, bet
Rise from the ashes, bet it all
Go!
We go hard!
I want it all!
다시 일어나, 파괴와 재생
Rise again, destruction and rebirth
죽지 않아, 전부 걸어
I won't die, bet it all
맞서 싸워, 시작이야
Fight back, it's just the beginning
Take the crown
끝까지 달려가
Run to the very end
Rule the game
We'll hit that high
Snake eyes, snake eyes
같이 춤을 춰 봐, 이렇게
Dance with me like this
멈출 순 없어, 같이 dance all night
Can't stop, let's dance all night
준비~!
Ready~!
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just a new beginning
Look at the cards we dealing
Sometimes it takes a villain
Snake eyes, the time is nigh
Fly high with pride
and leave all fears behind!
Ahhhhhh!
It's finally out!
I hope you all enjoyed my new song, Snake Eyes!
Snake Eyes! Snake eyes! Snake eyes! Snake eyes!
This is... has been such a long process in the making, I can't even talk.
I'm exhausted, but also, I'm so happy. It's finally out!
My newest song, Snake Eyes, is what I just performed.
Not only is it... not the first time that, you know, I've written a lot of the lyrics from scratch for it, you know...
...but also, it's my first time choreographing, you know, a multi-member song, multi-member with, you know, the two back dancers.
I'm so happy! I did it!
I hope you guys enjoyed it. Now, very important, pay attention.
The MV of this new song is also going to be premiering very soon after the live is over...
...and it is going to be my first ever 3D music video!
Oh, so excited. やっとね、新曲がちょっとね、あのー公開するので
I'm so excited! My new song is finally going to be released...
めっちゃくちゃ嬉しいです。
...so I'm incredibly happy.
えっと、この後ライブの後ね、あの初の3D MVもプレミアするので
Also, after this live stream, my first-ever 3D MV will premiere,
あの見届けてください、お願いします。
so please be there to watch it.
歌詞、えー英語の歌詞はほぼあの自分で書いたので
For the lyrics, I wrote almost all of the English lyrics myself,
あと韓国語도네、あの頑張って歌ったんで、あの聴いてください。
and I also worked hard on singing the Korean parts, so please listen to it.
Streaming will also begin shortly after as well. It should be, um... local, local time midnight, I never know anything, but...
...it'll happen soon. So please make sure to check it out afterwards!
Oh, I hope I did okay. I don't know, I was stressed about the choreography for a very long time, but...
Now it's time! It's the thing you've all been waiting for!
Merch showcase! グッズ紹介に入りたいと思います！
A merch showcase! I'd like to get right into the merch showcase!
This is the lineup for this time! Ta-dah!
Woah!
Hakos Baelz 2026 birthday merch, birthday merch, this is what the full set looks like!
フルセットはこんな感じです！
This is what the full set looks like!
Uh, let's look at them one by one. This is what the full set looks like, and then we can go through them one by one.
What do we have first? First up, 最初は...
What do we have first? First up, first is...
何でしょう？
What could it be?
We have the [ReCOLOR] rubber mat!
Look at that beauty! This illustration is, of course, by my beloved...
...mama, Mika Pikazo-sensei. 今年も描いてくださってありがとうございます。
...mama, Mika Pikazo-sensei. Thank you so much for drawing it for me this year as well.
Um, I just thought, you know, my very first birthday merch was also actually... had like a rubber mat in it,
Um, I just thought, you know, my very first birthday merch actually had a rubber mat in it,
and since, you know, I have a new outfit, I thought it was only fitting that, you know, we have another rubber mat...
...for me to switch. I, I really want this, so that's why.
...for me to switch out. I really wanted this, so that's why.
I wanted it. And, you know, you can use it for Holocard!
Also look at this, and it is really pretty.
Look at it! It's so pretty!
Thank you so much!
あの、ママ、今年もね、Mikaママにイラスト描いてくださったので、
My mama, Mika Pikazo, also drew the illustration for me this year,
あざます！
so thank you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ぜひぜひ買ってください！
Please make sure to get one!
And what's the next item? Second is...
Ta-da!
The recolor plushie keychain!
Designed after my new outfit!
I've always wanted, like, a mini plushie
that I came out with.
You know, I have some, but I think
it was just... it was really fitting because I have a new outfit.
And I wanted a plushie in the new outfit.
I can take her around places,
you know, and, you know, you can photograph her, chuck her, I don't know,
take... pat her, I don't know, whatever you want to do.
But it's a plushie keychain,
so it comes with a ball chain so you can attach it to your bag!
And she's so cute!
Look at those squishy cheeks!
めっちゃ可愛いでしょ？キー、あの、
Isn't it so super cute? The plushie...
ぬいぐるみキーホルダーなんで、なんかカバンに
Since it's a plushie keychain,
つけたりとかね、できるので、
you can attach it to your bag and stuff,
めちゃくちゃ可愛い感じになりました！あざます！
and it turned out so incredibly cute! Thank you!
えっと、次！
Let's see, next!
What is the next one?
これです！
It's this!
The Lil Plushie Shed Pouch!
It is a pouch.
It is a pouch for the plushie
if you get both. It's like a set, you know?
Because, you know, you want to take your little Bae out into the world,
but what if she gets dirty?
You know, or like, you know, you don't want her
to get snagged on a corner and she rips.
You got to protect your little Bae.
So you have a Lil Plushie Shed
to house your little Bae!
But it fits perfectly, and you know,
you can use it. The design is also really cool as well.
Next!
Last but not least,
is something very special. It is a voice pack,
but it is my first ever
ASMR voice pack!
I get really embarrassed doing ASMR stuff, but I just thought,
you know, since it's a special occasion, maybe it'd be nice to have my very first ASMR voice pack.
It features an intimate scene
with you guys after the live show. So if you want to,
you know, check it out, please do!
僕、初、初のASMRボイス、
This is my first-ever ASMR voice,
シナリオボイスなんで、
a scenario voice pack, so...
もし気になってる方はぜひ
if you are interested,
聞いてください！
please give it a listen!
ありがとうございます！ It's called 'Forever Your Bae'.
Thank you so much! It's called "Forever Your Bae".
恥ずかしい...
So embarrassing...
Anyway, here are the full set bonuses!
Ta-da!
The postcard!
You get a Limited Edition, which... the Limited Edition, sorry,
features a hand-signed autograph and also a handwritten message
from yours truly,
just as an extra way to say thank you very much.
And the Standard Version comes with the foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message.
Arms are about to... about to die, but it's alright!
Thank you so much!
えっと、と、とく、とく、
Um, b-b-bonus, bonus...
やばい、読め、漢字が、漢字が何だっけ？
Oh no, I can't read it! What was this kanji again?
特典はこちらです！
The bonus is this!
あざます！ポストカード、
Thank you! The postcard,
えっと、あの、
um, let's see...
じ、じ、
H-h-hand...
直筆サインとメッセージがあります。ありがとうございます！
It has a handwritten autograph and message! Thank you!
Oh my god, my brain is just... it's gone. I'm so tired.
But anyway, um, I think that's it.
Oh wait, no, there's also a bonus voice! Wait, I forgot.
So with the full set, there is a bonus voice pack
that is also ASMR.
That's on top of the already ASMR voice pack,
just a little extra thing to say thank you.
That's it.
I'm embarrassed. Anyway, yes.
そういうわけです！ありがとうございます！はい！
So that's how it is! Thank you so much! Yes!
Um... Yes.
Before we continue, I guess
there is a little bit after, so I'm going to go put my jacket on real quick,
if that's okay. I'll be right back.
ちょっと着替えてきます。
I'll go change real quick.
ターーーム！戻ってきました！
Ta-da! I'm back!
ただいまです！えっと、
I'm back! Um,
just put on my jacket.
I'm so happy!
That you know, I got to do another birthday live this year, even though it's not really my birthday.
Um, I'm so happy that I got to show my new outfit!
I'm just happy that I got a new outfit!
It's so easy to dance in, I love the way it looks.
And today I got to dance with so many
of my friends! It was so much fun.
I got to challenge myself. It's always an amazing, amazing experience
being able to do a birthday live.
いや、今日ね、あの、いっぱいメンバーと一緒に踊って、めちゃくちゃ嬉しくて、
Actually, today, dancing with so many members made me so happy,
もう、新衣装もめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて、もう、とにかく嬉しいです！
and I'm so happy about the new outfit too, I'm just so happy!
あの、みんなもね、
And everyone, too...
There's a lot of planning that goes into these,
you know, a lot of staff and everyone. スタッフさんのね、
lots of staff and everyone. The staff members,
みんなもね、ありがとう！
and everyone, thank you!
Everyone's...
力...
...power...
が必要。もう、なんだこれ、
...is needed. Wait, what is this...
もう英語か日本語かもう分かんないっす。
...I don't even know if I'm speaking English or Japanese anymore.
すいません、はい。
Sorry about that.
I'm just mixing up my languages, but...
Please do check out the new song MV that's coming out shortly,
I'm really, really proud of it.
But that's kind of it. That's all I have for today.
But! There is a final encore song that I wanted to sing,
that I think really sums up today's live.
So, please stay to the end. Please listen.
Please don't go anywhere.
ちょっとこの後、最後の一曲あります。
After this, there is one last song.
今日のテーマにピッタリの曲だと思いますので、最後まで聴いてください。
I think it fits today's theme perfectly, so please listen to the end.
はい！
Yes!
あと新曲のMVも見てくださいね。
Also, please watch the new song's MV as well.
じゃあ、最後の曲、ラストの曲どうぞ。
So, here is the last song. Please enjoy.
魂の色は
I wonder what the color of my soul is...
何色ですか
...What color is it?
Thank you for coming to my live tonight!
I hope I brought some color to your day!
最後まで盛り上がっていこうぜ！
Let's keep the energy high until the very end!
もういっそ 折れたままで
I'd rather keep it broken,
捨てるほど 逃げ出すほど
the more I try to throw it away and run,
強くないよ ほら
see, I'm just not that strong.
もう一度 鼓動、高鳴る
Once again, my heart is beating louder.
何が正しいかなんて
What is the right thing to do?
わからないけど
I still don't know, but...
形のないものばかりが 大切になっていく
Only things without shape become precious to me.
飾らない言葉だけが
Only unadorned words...
強く結ばれてる
...are tied tightly together.
また躓いて転がって
I tripped and fell again,
それでも砕けない
but I still won't shatter.
魂の色は 何色ですか
What is the color of my soul?
ただ傷ついて強がって
I just get hurt and put up a tough front,
それでも見つけたいよ
but I still want to find it.
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
I am confirming the shape of my soul.
深い地の底で一人
Alone at the bottom of a deep earth,
扉と鍵を探す
I search for a door and a key.
おとぎ話は ほら
See, the fairy tales...
泡の様に全部消えて 葛藤、残像だけ
...disappeared like bubbles, leaving only struggles and afterimages.
次のページへ
On to the next page.
伸びて行く枝葉が分かれて
The growing branches split...
それぞれの道を行く
...and go their separate ways.
寂しい思い出だけが
Only lonely memories...
強く根を張ってる
...are taking deep root.
また貫いて失って
I pierced through and lost again,
それでも挫けない
but I still won't give up.
心はどこに 器はどこに
Where is my heart? Where is the vessel?
ただ残されて抜け落ちて
Simply left behind and falling away,
それでも伝えたいよ
but I still want to tell you.
魂の日々を
Of the days of my soul,
魂の意思を
of the will of my soul...
ずっと ずっと
forever and ever...
ずっと ずっと ずっと
forever and ever and ever...
魂の色は
I wonder what the color of my soul is...
何色ですか
...What color is it?
赤い色ですか
Is it red?
青い色ですか
Is it blue?
魂の色は
The color of my soul...
何色ですか
...What color is it?
透明な過去に
In a transparent past,
不透明な明日に
in an opaque tomorrow...
生きるあなたは 何色ですか
...what color are you, living on?
また躓いて転がって
I tripped and fell again,
それでも砕けない
but I still won't shatter.
魂の色は 何色ですか
I wonder what the color of my soul is...
ただ傷ついて強がって
I just get hurt and put up a tough front,
それでも見つけたいよ
but I still want to find it.
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
I am confirming the shape of my soul.
...確かめてやるよ
...I'll make sure of it
ずっと
forever...
Wow Wow
Woah, woah, woah
ずっと
forever...
Wow Wow
Woah, woah, woah
ずっと
forever...
Wow Wow
Woah, woah, woah
ずっと
forever...
Wow Wow
Woah, woah, woah
NEW 3D OUTFIT?!
ReCOLOR - Hakos Baelz Birthday Live 2026